SHELDON: You know, I've been thinking
about time travel again.
Why? Did you hit a roadblock
with invisibility?
(Sheldon:)Put it on the back burner.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, it occurs to me,
if I ever did perfect a time machine...
...I'd go into the past
and give it to myself.
(Sheldon:)Thus eliminating the need for me
to invent it in the first place.
(Sheldon:)- Interesting.
- Yeah, it really takes the pressure off.
(Leonard:)Sounds like a breakthrough.
Should I call Science
and tell them to hold the cover?
(Sheldon:)It's time travel, Leonard.
I will have done that.
(Leonard:)I guess congratulations are in order.
(Sheldon:)No, congratulations
will have been in order.
(Sheldon:)You know,
I'm not going to enjoy this party.
LEONARD:
I know, I'm familiar with you.
SHELDON: The last party,
Professor Finkleday cornered me...
(Sheldon:)...and talked about spelunking
for 45 minutes.
(Leonard:)Yes, I was there.
(Sheldon:)You know what's interesting
about caves?
- What?
- Nothing.
We'll avoid Finkleday, meet the new head,
congratulate him, shake his hand and go.